Dean, meet Sharon Solaye.
Dean, 见一下Sharon Solaye.
She's our concierge.
她是咱们的前台(concierge).
Dean is our college intern for the summer.
Dean是咱们的大学实习生 对于暑期
Nice to meet you, Dean.
很高兴认识你, Dean
Hello. Goodbye.
你好. 拜拜.
Bye bye.
拜拜
William, this is Dean Johnson.
William, 这是Dean Johnson.
He's the new intern. Dean, William.
他是新来的实习生. Dean, (这是)William.
Hi, Dean. Welcome to the ...
Hi, Dean. 欢迎来到...
Nice to meet you.
很高兴认识你.
He isn't here.
他不在这里
Hello. What's all this?
嗨. 这都是什么?
There you are. Meet our new intern.
你在这里呀. 见一下咱们新来的实习生.
My name's Dean Johnson.
我的名字是Dean Johnson.
I'm Simon Wilkinson,
我是Simon Wilkinson,
manager of the restaurant.
餐厅的经理.
How do you do?
你好
That's Kevin. He's our bartender.
那是Kevin. 他是咱们的调酒师.
Kev! this is Dean.
Kev, 这是Dean.
Hi.  -Hi.
嗨  -嗨,
Are you new?
你是新来的?
Yeah, I'm the new intern.
Yeah, 我是新来的实习生.
Have you met everybody?
你见过每个人了吗?
Dean?
Well, see you later...
Well, 回头见...
I'm sorry, what's your name again?
不好意思, 你叫什么来着?